Neha Erasmus African Union High Level Implementation Panel Papers MS207
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negotiations records, 2010 -- 2013; MS207.002; 911 Digital Object(s)
  - April 2013 negotiations, MS207.002.00967
    - Visas, 2013; MS207.002.01009
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Simon Komi, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01018
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Walid Mohamed, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01019
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Yasir Arman, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01020
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN Zeinab Eldai, 2013-04-18; MS207.002.01021
      - AUHIP visa letter SPLMN, 2013-04-21; MS207.002.01022
      - Proposed Agenda for Meeting on the Implementation of the Framework Agreement on the Status of Nationals of the Other State and Related Matters, 2013-04-07; MS207.002.01023